領 銜 主 演
艾 爾 · 帕 西 諾          羅 伯 特 · 德 尼 羅
片 名: 盜 火 線
又 譯: 烈 火 悍 將
編劇 及 導演
邁 克 爾 · 曼
你現在可以把她留在走廊裏
Yeah, you can leave her in the hallway for now.
- 穩住這兒  - 便攜X光機在哪兒
- Stabilizing here. - Where's the portable x-ray?
支票  信用卡  還是現金
Check, charge or cash?
現金
Cash. And, uh...
發票寫土珊市積氏拆卸公司
...make it out to Jack's Demolition, Tucson.
總數是七百八十八點三元
Seven eighty-eight thirty.
好了
Okay.
嘿
Hey.
和我吃早餐嗎
Taking me to breakfast?
不行  我得去見博高
I can't, I'm meeting Bosko.
嘿  雲信
Hey, Vincent.
- 媽媽  我的髮夾呢  - 嘿  寶貝
- Mom, where are my barrettes? - Hi, sweetie.
- 我看見在廚房桌子上  - 不在那兒  我看過了
- I saw them on the kitchen table. - They're not there. I already checked.
- 喝咖啡嗎  - 今天不用上學嗎
- Want me to make coffee? - No school today?
爸爸帶我去新大廈  然後吃午餐
My dad's taking me to the new building and then to lunch.
到沙發墊子下找
Try under the cushions on the sofa.
他遲了半小時
He's already a half an hour late.
他會出現還是像上次那樣爽約
He gonna show? Or that son of a bitch gonna stand her up like last time?
- 我煮咖啡  - 沒時間了
- I'll make coffee. - I'm out of time, babe.
我的髮夾不在沙發里
Mom, where are my barrettes? They're not in the couch.
戴藍色那一個
Wear the blue ones.
我不想戴  顏色不配襯
I don't wanna wear the blue ones. They don't match.
- 浴室找過沒有  - 找過了
- Did you check in your bathroom? - I checked everywhere.
- 我該怎辦  - 去找
- Well, what do you want me to do? - Find them.
- 媽  留心  - 好了  寶貝
- Mom, pay attention. - All right, sweetie, all right. What?
- 爸爸會到來的  - 好啦
- Daddy's gonna be here. - Okay, he's gonna...
我來不及準備  我可不能遲到
I'm not gonna be ready. I can't be late.
- 你不會遲到的  - 我會遲到的
- You won't be late. - No, I will be late.
若一起找  爸到來前會找到
Okay. Before Daddy comes, we can find them if we look together.
- 沒事的  寶貝  - 不
- It's all right, baby. It's all right. - No.
沒事的
It's all right. It's all right.
我們一起找
We'll find them together, you and me. We'll find them together.
放心  他到來前我們會找到
Just relax. He won't come before we find them. I promise you.
給我添一杯
Hey. Give me another refill.
再添一杯
Now he wants a refill.
- 你叫什麼  - 榮谷
- What's your name? - Waingro.
你是米高吧
You're Michael, huh?
你們常一起合作嗎
You guys always work together?
經常合作
All the time.
- 合作無間吧  - 是的
- Real tight crew, huh? - Real tight.
若今次順利  我會考慮再做
Yeah, if this works good, I'd consider going again, you know.
好的  別再說話  滑頭
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
- 他怎麼樣  - 百分百滿意
- How's he doing? - A hundred percent.
很準時
Right on schedule.
威尼斯街右轉
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
- 我們離你一英里半  - 好的
- We're a mile and a half from you. - Okay.
越過行車快線  離你三百碼
Just crossed over the number-one lane, 300 yards from you now.
- 準備  - 準備就緒
- Get set. - I am.
戴上面具
Put that on.
行動
Here we go.
有劫案  我們遇劫
Two eleven! Two eleven! We're being held up!
裝甲車遇劫  已通知了警方
Two-eleven alarm. Armored car.
有三分鐘
There's the call. Three minutes.
離開
Clear!
只剩八十秒
Eighty seconds left!
退後
Get back. Get back.
Get back!
滑頭  他耳朵流血  聽不到的
Hey, Slick, you see that shit coming out of their ears?
別胡來
They can't fucking hear you. Cool it.
找到了
I got it.
到手
Got it.
你要和我過不去
You had to fuck with me.
You wanna fuck with me?
快撤  你在做什麼
Come on! What the fuck are you doing?
- 你幹了什麼  - 迫不得已  夥計
- What did you do? - I had to, man.
- 他作勢要攻擊  - 快走
- Guy was making a move. - Let's go.
我操你媽
Dumb motherfucker.
- 請退後  先生  - 我聽到他們了
- Step back, please, sir. - I heard them.
一百六十萬
A million six.
每元分四角  你可得六十四萬
Forty cents on the dollar, 640,000 to you.
這是十五萬的預支
Here's a 150 front money.
其餘的兩三天後付
Get you the rest in two, three days.
知道是誰擁有的嗎
Know who owned these?
馬莉堡股票及投資公司
Malibu Equity and Investments.
羅傑·宏山  在開曼群島擁有銀行
Roger Van Zant. Owns banks in the Caymans.
替國外毒販洗錢  並負責投資事務
Runs investment portfolios for offshore drug money. Stuff like that.
- 那麼  - 你偷了他的債券
- So? - So you ripped off his bearer bonds.
他買了保險
He's got insurance.
他可以獲得百分百的保險賠償
That's the point. He collects 100 percent from the insurance.
也許他向我們購回債券
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds back from us for 60 percent of their value.
六折價購回  再賺四成
And make 40 percent on top of the 100 percent.
債券賣給他  你可以再得到三十二萬
Sell it back to him instead of going to the street. That's an extra 320,000 to you.
試試看
Try it on him.
- 祈素來電話  - 關於什麼事
- Kelso called. - About what?
他找人參與買賣
A score he's putting out and wants you to look at.
我不需要  我自己有買賣
What do I need his score for? I got my own.
說錢無法追查而且超過千萬元
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
- 明天九時  - 那兒發生了什麼事
- 9 a.m. tomorrow. - What happened out there?
別問了
Don't ask.
找到救傷車了嗎
Find the ambulance?
- 在四條街外遭棄掉  - 在二十二街的花店門口
- Dumped it four blocks from here. - 22nd Street between Figueroa and Flower.
縱火燒掉  槍和衣服化為灰燼
They torched it. Burned everything. The guns, clothes, everything.
調查員仍在現場工作
Investigators are still working the scene...
記者用直升機
They were airborne. Taped the last few seconds...
拍下幾秒的黑白片
...of the black-and-whites doing demolition derby.
救傷車兩星期前被偷
Stolen out of Fresno two weeks ago.
黃色車是前天在惠帝爾被偷
Yellow pickup truck out of whittier day before yesterday.
你負責此案  還是由分局調查
You taking this one, lieutenant, or does it stay in Division?
這一宗是便利店劫案嗎
This look like gangbangers working the local 7-11 to you?
- 搶劫及兇殺組接手調查  - 全歸你了
- Robbery-Homicide's taking it. Yeah. - All yours.
三名司機目擊事發  只看見戴上面具的人
We got three motorists. All they saw were men with masks. They were distant.
那邊的電視流浪漢距離現場很近
Console TV man over there however, he was closer.
他能認出任何人嗎
He ID anybody?
他躲起來了  聽到大部分對話
Well, he was hiding. He heard it mostly.
他們呢
Okay. What about them?
電視漢說這人在胡言亂語
Right. Now, according to TV man, this guy started mouthing off.
- 很聰明  - 有人把護衛叫作滑頭
- Smart. - Yeah, somebody called a guard "Slick".
- 滑頭  - 是的
- Slick? - Yeah.
我認為此人  想拿綁在足踝的槍
Now, this guy... I figure this guy went for that holdout piece, ankle holster, right?
由這兒
From here.
開槍
Bang. Bang. Bang, bang, bang.
子彈由這兒穿出
To his side.
這人看來好像是胸部中槍
This guy here has got what appears to be a double-tap entry wound to the sternum.
從頭的傷勢看似乎是近距離被殺
Tattooing around the head wound, scorched bone, close range.
很可能是處決
Probably executed.
一百六十萬的債券被盜  他們沒拿走現金
And it was a million six in bearer bonds, and they ignored the loose cash.
因為他們沒時間  時間緊迫
Because they had no time, because they were on a clock.
他們知道警方何時會到達
Which means they knew our response time to a 2-11...
聽警方廣播  把車截停  進入
...had our air, immobilized it, entered...
及在三分鐘內逃走
...escaped in under three minutes.
這是好地點  有良好逃走路線
It's a good spot here. We got good escape routes.
- 兩條公路在四分之一英里以內  - 交通錄影呢
- Two freeways within a quarter of a mile. - Traffic video camera?
可能給弄壞了  但還是查看一下
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
你能認出手法嗎
You recognize the M.O.?
手法  是職業劫匪所為
M.O. is that they're good.
他們殺死兩名警衛  犯了一級謀殺罪
Once it escalated into a murder-one beef for all of them...
之後便不再遲疑
...after they killed the first two guards, they didn't hesitate...
殺了第三名  因為橫豎也是犯罪
...popped guard number three because what difference does it make?
為何留下證人呢
Why leave a living witness?
他們會毫不遲疑  心狠手辣
Drop of a hat, these guys will rock 'n' roll.
定向炸藥
The shape charge.
顯示劫匪的技術是精通的
The shape charge indicates that they are technically proficient.
足以使他們在途中下手
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
我們要找偷值錢東西的劫匪
So let's start looking for recent high-line burglaries that have mystified us.
查滑頭這個綽號
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI.
名單可能很長  但還是要查
You're gonna get the phone book. Do it anyway.
誰賣出債券
Who's moving the bearer bonds?
查慣常接贓者 你和我查古和陶
Check the usual fences. You and I will check Cusamano and Torena.
我要你查高士丹及艾化魯  和鑒證科緊密合作
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro. Hang in with Forensics.
向炸彈組查問用的是什麼炸藥
From the bomb squad, I want the explosive.
若是罕見的  便可追查發售來源
If we're lucky, it's exotic. We can trace the sale.
你別伸手進那人的口袋
Get your hand out of that man's pocket, Rachel.
噢  雲信
Oh, Vince.
有誰要吃批餅
Want some pie?
我要上廁所
Gotta go to the john.
他作勢攻擊  我要先下手為強
Look, I had to get it on, man. He was making a move. I had to get it on.
他那份在車上  我們的均分了
Split's in the car. I took out of ours evenly...
以便全數給他
...to make up for his full end.
因為我想立即分給他  打發這雜種
Because I wanna pay off and get rid of this motherfucker right now.
好的
Okay.
等一等
Hold it!
嘿
Hey.
- 其餘的錢呢  - 時候不早了
- Where's the rest? - We're late.
你打扮得很漂亮  我想在這兒和你做愛
Ooh, you look too good to go out. I could just jump you right here.
- 錢呢  - 還給外圍馬的人了
- Where is it? - Uh, squared the bookies, baby.
幾天後還會有錢  放心吧
There's more in a couple days, so don't sweat it. We really are late.
少胡說  你一定是說笑
Yeah, come on, you gotta be kidding me.
親愛的  就為了區區八千元值得冒這個險嗎
Honey, it ain't worth the risks you take for 8000.
危險和報酬要成正比
Like in risk versus reward, baby.
走吧  拿上你的外衣
Let's go. Get your coat.
無謂再說  你心智還沒成熟
There is no point talking to you. All you are is a child growing older.
什麼意思
What's that supposed to mean?
我們不像成年人那樣有進步
It means we're not making forward progress like real grown-up adults, living our lives.
因為我嫁給了一個賭徒
I'm married to a gambling junkie who won't listen.
上車吧
Charlene, get in the fucking car.
我怎麼可以這樣下去的
What am I doing in this rat-bastard situation?
你不用  你離開這裏時
You're not! What do you want from me? Leave the bankbook and car keys...
留下銀行存折和車匙
...in the kitchen on your way out. Are we going, or am I going alone?
你留著吧  我只帶多明一起走
You could keep that other crap but Dominick would go with me.
你別妄想
Don't you even think about...
陶·亞拔覆電話了
Yeah. Tell me Albert Torena called back.
- 陶·亞拔有給雲信電話嗎  - 沒有
- Albert Torena call Vincent? - No.
沒有  有報告
No. Report came in.
炸藥是拆毀用的
The explosive was Dynex, linear-shaped charge used in demolition.
可在內華達  亞利桑拿  新墨西哥州買到
You can pick it up with a driver's license in Nevada, Arizona, New Mexico.
- 太普通  難以追查來源  - 那太好了
- Too common to trace a sale, Vincent. - Oh, that's wonderful.
你沒事吧
Are you all right?
怎麼了  你去了哪兒
What happened? Where you been?
工作
Work.
羅蘭的父親有來嗎
Lauren's dad show up?
沒來電話  沒出現  我們等你直至十時半
Didn't call, didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
這人知道他女兒是怎樣的嗎
Now, does this guy have any idea what's going on with his kid?
我不知道
I don't know.
該死的混蛋
Fucking jerk.
她沒事吧
Well, is she okay?
她整天在房內
She's been in her room all day.
她很難過  我亦不開心
So no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
我弄了晚餐  四小時前為我們煮了
Uh, I made dinner for us, four hours ago. Um...
我設法替我們保持一貫的情緒  你退卻了
Every time I try to maintain a consistent mood between us, you withdraw.
在威尼斯大道旁邊躺著三名死者  彩鈿
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
對不起
I'm sorry...
若那可惡的雞
...if the goddamn chicken...
給煮過了頭
...got overcooked.
丹麥的七個人  是此案的關鍵被告
...seven men in Denmark, to a key defendant here.
- 你找到了嗎  - 還沒有
- Did you find it? - Not yet.
找到了
There it is.
過了這裏  就在某一處
It's over here, somewhere.
- 室內設計呢  - 在後牆那邊
- Interior design? - It's on the back wall.
- 要咖啡嗎  - 好的
- Coffee, sir? - Please.
請把奶遞給我
Will you pass the cream?
- 謝謝  - 你買了什麼
- Thanks. - What did you get?
什麼
What?
你在看什麼書
What are you reading?
關於金屬的書
Book about metals.
鈦的應力折斷
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
你幹什麼工作的
What kind of work you do?
你為何對我看什麼書幹什麼工作感興趣
Lady, why are you so interested in what I read or what I do?
我在店中看到過你
I've seen you in the store from time to time.
什麼店
What store?
書店  我在那兒工作
Hennessey + Ingalls. I work there.
呃
Uh...
若你不想交談  好的  抱歉打擾你了
If you don't wanna talk to me, it's okay. I'm sorry I bothered you.
我不想無禮  只是認不出你
I didn't mean to be rude. I didn't recognize you.
我是營業員  專門推銷金屬的  我叫尼爾
I work in metals. I'm a salesman. My name's Neil.
我叫伊荻
I'm Eady.
你喜歡在書店工作
You like working there?
是的
Sure.
我買書有折扣  亦有我行內的書
I get a discount and there's a whole section of books in my area.
是哪一行業
What area's that?
平面設計
Graphic design.
晚上設計信紙及商標
I do, um, letterheads and logotypes at night...
白天在書店工作直至能藉此謀生
...and the store's a day job till I get enough going.
你為誰設計呢
Who do you do that for?
餐廳
Uh, a restaurant.
我設計他們的餐牌  以及
I did their menus, and, um...
為小唱片公司設計
...a small, uh, record label.
鐳射唱片封套  目前已設計了兩張
CDs. I've done two so far.
你上學校受訓嗎
You go to school for that?
是的
Heh, yeah.
- 我念過巴桑學校  - 在哪兒
- Yeah, I went to Parsons. - Where's that?
紐約市
New York City.
你在這兒住了多久
How long you been out here?
約一年
About a year.
喜歡這兒嗎
You like it?
不算喜歡  我為工作才來這兒
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
- 你住在附近嗎  - 不
- Live in this neighborhood? - Ah, no...
我住在日落廣場上面山上
...I live, um, kind of above Sunset Plaza.
租住一所小房子
It's actually kind of... It's a little house that I rent.
頗為破舊  但景觀極佳
And it's just kind of run-down, but a beautiful, beautiful view.
你呢
What about you?
- 我住在這兒  - 很有趣
- I live up here. - That's very funny.
你的家人原本從哪兒來
So where's your family from originally?
嗯
Um...
是蘇格蘭及愛爾蘭裔
I'm Scotch-Irish.
一七零零年末期移居美國東南部
They, um, emigrated to Appalachia in the late 1700s.
你從哪兒來
Where are you from?
三藩市灣區
The Bay Area.
家人在那兒
Are your folks there?
母親很久前死了  我父親  我也不知他在哪兒
Uh, my mother died a long time ago, and my father, I don't know where he is.
我有個兄弟
Got a brother somewhere.
你的家人關係很緊密吧
You have a tight family. I can tell.
- 是的  - 是嗎
- Yep. - Right?
你說得對
You're right.
是啊
Yeah...
燈火通明的城市
City of lights.
在菲濟  有一種會發光的海藻  每年浮出水面一次
In Fiji, they have these iridescent algae. They come out once a year in the water.
這城市的燈正是如此
That's what it looks like out there.
你到過菲濟
You been there?
沒有  我終有一天會去
No, I'm going there someday.
是嗎
Oh, yeah?
你常旅遊
You travel a lot?
- 是的  - 旅遊使你寂寞
- Yeah. - Traveling makes you lonely?
我一個人  可我並不寂寞
I... I'm alone. I am not lonely.
你呢
You?
很寂寞
I get lonely.
亞拔
Albert!
- 糟了  - 亞拔
- Shit. - Albert.
你為何來這兒
Vincent, what you doing coming here, man?
你瘋了嗎
You crazy? This ain't Disneyland.
你該回覆我電話的  你去了哪兒
You were supposed to get back to me last night, Albert. Where the fuck you been?
- 我無法脫身  - 我們侵犯他的民權吧
- I couldn't break free, Vincent. You know. - Let's violate his ass right now.
我幫你忙  你卻不幫我  是這樣嗎
I do for you, you don't do for me, is that it?
我整晚外出
Vincent, man, I swear, I was out all night, man.
為你刺探消息
I'm hitting like one of them flamingo-matador guys.
此事和我無關
Flamingo? That's got nothing to do with me.
我順利為你找到線索
I was cutting it real smooth. I'm generating leads and shit for you.
- 我很棒  - 你胡說
- I'm a dancer, man. You know. - Bullshit.
我傳呼你一整天  我討厭這樣做
I paged your ass all day. I can't stand paging.
你又再是癮君子  注射毒品
You're a speed freak, jacking methamphetamine again.
我有濫用藥物的問題  心領吧
Where is your empathy, brother? It's a substance-abuse problem.
我昨天對你心領
Empathy was yesterday.
你今天卻浪費我時間
Today you're wasting my motherfucking time.
- 聽著  - 你戀愛了嗎
- Vincent, man, look... - Did you fall in love?
你是否戀愛和到別處去啦
Come on. Did you fall in love last night and you went off somewhere?
- 雲信  - 我會接受這解釋
- Vincent... - Just tell me that. I'll settle for it.
- 我會信的  - 雲信
- I'll buy that. - Vincent.
把消息告訴我
Give me all you got!
- 雲信  - 把資料對我說
- Vincent... - Give me all you got!
我發誓  我哥哥裏察會跟你說
I swear, man, my brother, man. My brother Richard's gonna talk to you.
你是說裏察嗎
I heard "Richard"?
- 他會和你說的  - 裏察
- He's gonna talk to you. - Richard?
- 裏察  - 裏察
- Richard. - Richard.
- 他今晚會見你  - 他在這兒
- He's gonna meet you, I swear, tonight. - He's not here, is he?
- 不  他會見你  - 現在不行嗎
- No, he's gonna meet you tonight. - Tonight? What happened to now?
我懇求他  因為我知道你今早會到來
I... I... I implored him because I knew you was coming this a.m.
- 胡說  - 沒有  我發誓
- This is a bunch of bullshit. - No, no, I swear.
他不肯的  因為他在鳳凰城
He said no because he in Phoenix.
- 啊  - 我發誓
- Ahh. - But this, man, I swear... I swear, man.
我到了鳳凰城後
By the time I get to Phoenix,
他會起程
He'll be risin',
可能留下字條  貼在門上
He'll probably leave a note right on the door
我只能令他今晚見你
Tonight's the best I can do for you, man.
今晚在艾華瓦度街BJ夜總會
You know? He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado...
凌晨二時  你去吧
...at 2 a.m. Be there.
你亦要到
You be there too.
不行  我有事要辦
Vincent, I can't be there, man. I got things to do, Vincent.
- 我有事辦  要到別處  - 嘿
- I got things to do, places to be. I got... - Hey, hey, hey.
你要去
Be there.
你別浪費我的時間
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
是什麼買賣
What is it?
是銀行
It's a bank.
星期四會存錢以便分發各分行
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution to all the other branches...
應付星期五支付薪金的支票
...to cover Friday payroll checks.
總行夾萬內星期四總放滿現鈔
So on Thursdays, the command branch has got a full whack.
- 在途中下手還是劫銀行  - 由正門進入
- On the prowl or strong? - Strong. Through the front door.
有多少人
How many guys?
連司機四人  走進銀行  得手便走
Four, or three plus a driver. Walk in, knock them over, walk out.
你要先拿十萬
And you want a 100,000 advance...
事成後分一成
...against a 10-percent cut for that?
聽似是西部牛仔劫銀行  他們按動警鐘
Sounds like an address to a cowboy score. They hit the holdup alarms...
我得在之前離去
...I gotta get out before the cops show. What is that?
他們可按動三個遇劫警鐘
They hit three holdup alarm systems.
兩個一般警鐘和一個蜂窩式的
Two telco and a cellular.
但訊號無法傳送出去  因為
See, but the signals aren't going anywhere because...
之前一晚  你潛進銀行  破壞警報系統的電腦
See, the night before, you cut in and trick out the alarm-system computer...
使電腦及錄影裝置在你下手前二十分鐘關掉
...to turn itself and the video recorders off 20 minutes before you walk in the door.
你有建築及電子藍圖嗎
Architectural, electrical-engineering plans?
我有  我建造電腦板  直駁中央處理器
I got all that. Schematics, got the boards already built. They go straight into the CPU.
估計可有多少錢
What's the estimate?
一千兩百一十萬到一千兩百二十萬
12.1, 12.2 million.
我會參加
You're on.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我告訴你如何估計會有這筆錢
And to give you a little idea of where my estimates come from, this is a printout...
沒人知道貨是你的
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
我讓你得保險全數
Be that as it may, my way you get 100 percent from the insurance company...
賠償以六成價  把債券回購
...and take the bonds from us at 60 cents on the dollar...
你可多賺四成
...and make yourself another 40 percent.
行動全無損失  我們均可賺大錢
Your operation doesn't skip a beat. Everybody makes out.
我同意
Sure, you got a deal.
好  若大家不喜歡便沒得益
Good, because there's no percentage if everyone gets their underwear in a twist.
要你的人給我電話  安排會面
Yeah, so you have your man call me and we'll set the meet.
行啊  可以
Yeah, okay.
高興和你通電話
Nice talking to you.
你要和他們交易嗎
You gonna deal with these guys?
江湖上可接受我偷自己的東西嗎
So word's out on the street it's okay to steal my stuff.
我會殺了這班渾蛋
I'm gonna kill the sons of bitches.
命哈利給我加那利群島的試算紙
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets for Canary Islands' offshore.
這些不是估計  是實在數字
That's not really an estimate. Those are exact figures.
我印出銀行過去兩月的現金帳
I have a printout of the, uh, cash flow of the bank for the past two months.
- 資料怎麼得來的  - 送上門的
- How'd you get this information? - Just comes to you.
資料府拾皆是
This stuff just flies through the air.
到處傳送  只需加以掌握便行
They send information out and it's beamed out all over the place.
我懂得掌握
All you have to do is know how to grab it. See, I know how to grab it.
這是我們要的  一千三百九十萬
Um... Okay, here we go. Thirteen-point-nine million.
- 我同意了  - 好啊
- I bought it. - Good.
我沒說錯吧
What did I tell you?
拿著
Here.
同意了  聯絡宏山  準備收錢吧
We're on. Call Van Zant, collect the money.
- 他怎麼樣  - 他是生意人
- How is he? - He's a businessman.
好吧
Okay.
- 鱷梨  - 鱷梨
- Avocado. - Avocado.
- 喂  - 是我
- Hello? - Yeah, hello.
基斯在我家中
Chris is at my place.
- 怎麼了  - 夫妻的爭吵
- What's wrong? - Husband-and-wife stuff.
我讓他睡醒再算
I'll let him sleep it off here.
你怎麼了
What happened to you?
- 你何時買傢俱  - 我有時間便買
- When you gonna get some furniture? - When I get around to it.
莎蓮要離開我
Charlene's gonna leave me.
為什麼
Why?
我無好好供養她
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
我們做買賣還不夠錢嗎
With everything we've been doing?
賭場及賭球賽使我身無分文
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
- 你何時會結婚  - 有時間再算
- When you gonna get an old lady? - When I get around to it.
你有外遇嗎
You got something else on the side?
沒固定的
Nothing regular.
她有外遇嗎
She got something else on the side?
- 沒有  - 你肯定嗎
- No. - You sure?
肯定
Yeah, I'm sure.
我不知你做什麼
I don't know what you're doing.
如占美說
Remember Jimmy MacAwain on the yard used to say:
你想當罪犯嗎
You wanna be making moves on the street?
要無牽掛  生活中不能有任何牽掛
Have no attachments. Allow nothing to be in your life...
風聲緊時便可拋下一切
...that you cannot walk out on in 30 seconds flat...
一走了之
...if you spot the heat around the corner.
記得嗎
Remember that?
她是我一生中最重要的
For me, the sun rises and sets with her, man.
是嗎
Yeah?
是的
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
我們從宏山那兒拿到錢
Today we take delivery of cash from Van Zant...
然後為劫銀行的事存錢給祈素
...then I drop our deposit on Kelso for this bank.
什麼銀行
Bank? What bank?
這白金的事如何  快成事了
What about the platinum thing? It's ready to fall.
那亦會進行  然後再劫銀行
That goes too, then the bank.
- 要吃早餐嗎  - 好啊
- You want some breakfast? - Yeah.
你沒事吧
Are you okay?
沒事
Yeah, sugar.
耶
Yeah.
- 是真的  - 好吧
- For real. - Okay.
我會好好的做
Gonna do good.
再見
I'll see you later.
你是索倫戈嗎  我是當·畢頓
You Solenko? I'm Don Breedan.
假釋官告訴我  你會有工作給我
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to come by here and see if you had a job for me.
- 你對工作嫻熟嗎  - 我燒烤很出色的
- You're familiar with this kind of operation? - Yeah, man. I'm a great grill man.
好  你洗抹廁所  洗碗碟
Good. Good for you. Here, you'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher...
收拾桌子
...bus tables and empty the garbage too.
你若煩我  我就舉報你藏毒酗酒或偷竊
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded, drunk or stealing.
很快舉報你違反假釋條例
And I will violate you back so fast your head will spin.
你給我薪金的百分之二十五作為回佣
Twenty-five percent of your take-home kicks back to me.
是規矩  問假釋官吧
Rules of the game. Call Grierson, check it out.
後面更衣
Change in the back.
你還等什麼
Well, what are you waiting for?
馬莉堡股票及投資
Malibu Equity and Investments.
- 羅傑·宏山  - 請稍等
- Yeah, Roger Van Zant. - Please hold.
我是羅傑·宏山
Yeah, this is Roger Van Zant.
我該有一些東西的
I'm supposed to collect something.
把你的號碼告訴我  會有人給你回覆電話
Give me your number, and somebody will call you right back from a different line.
818-133-6089
818-133-6089.
喂
Yep.
我有個包裹給你
I got a package for you.
明午二時半露天影院見
There's a drive-in on Centinela. 02:30 tomorrow.
只派一人單獨前來
Okay, just send one man, alone.
- 那人是誰  - 無名小卒
- Who was that guy? - Nobody.
那人是誰
Who the...? Who...? Who was that guy?
- 無名小卒  - 我要知道他是誰
- He's nobody. - I gotta know who he is. Who is he?
- 他是無名小卒  - 聽著
- He's nobody, Neil. - Listen, you...
他是賭城合法酒類營業員
He's a legit liquor wholesaler from Las Vegas.
- 馬·亞倫  - 基斯會與你和解
- Alan Marciano. - Chris is gonna straighten it up with you.
- 太遲了  我討厭他  - 閉嘴
- It's too late. I'm sick of it. I'm sick of it! - Shut up!
你再給基斯一次機會
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris one last shot.
若他再犯錯  我會資助你找地方住
After that, he fucks up, then I will finance setting you up myself...
住哪裏都行
...on my own, anywhere you want.
多明也會跟著你  我言出必行
Dominick will go with you. And my word counts.
但現在  你得再給他一次機會
But right now, you will give him the chance.
清洗一下  回家去
Clean up. Go home.
交出你的錢
Give me all your money.
你會因此而沒命的
One day you gonna get smoked with that shit.
殺我的不會是你
Ain't gonna be you, fool.
他一個人來
- He's coming in alone. Send him through. - Yeah, got it.
雲信
Vincent, hey, man.
這是我哥哥裏察  雲信
Vincent. This is my brother, Richard. Richard, Vincent.
- 裏察  - 沒關係
- Richard. - Yo, it's all right.
你有何消息告訴我
What have you got for me?
談正題前
Before we even get into that...
沙灘附近有人偷車
...there's this crew ripping rides all along the beach areas, all right?
在汽車裝飾店後
Now, the back of a trim shop on Irvine...
若週末有人前去那兒
...if somebody was to pay a little visit this weekend...
會找到一輛名貴跑車
...they might find two Turbos and a 911 Slope.
你參加賽車嗎
You're looking to rid yourself of your competition.
我是個好市民
Eh, I'm a good citizen.
我才不信  你有事要告訴我
I'm Donald Duck. So you got something to tell me or what?
你聽著  朋友
Check this out, coz.
我怎知若我說出你所想知的事
How do I know if I tell you what you need to know...
你會做我所想做的事
...you're gonna do what the fuck I need to get done?
裏察  韓很可靠的
Richard, man, Hanna is straight up, man. We do business all the time.
雜種  我不是你的朋友
I ain't your coz, you rat motherfucker.
你知道我說得出做得到  但我要先聽你有什麼話要說
And you know because I say so after I hear what the fuck you gotta tell me.
我操  明白嗎
Look here, man. You understand what I'm saying?
我說出來會沒命的
I can get killed for telling you this shit.
你溜狗時亦會沒命
Or you're gonna get killed walking your doggie.
好吧
All right.
我和這人在獄中相識
There's this cat I was locked up with in Folsom.
服刑兩三年  他出獄後我碰上他
Did a couple, two, three years. He got out and I ran into him.
那又怎樣
And so?
他是坐言起行的人
He's a big fiend for action.
若他不說  我便不會去想  可是
Now, if he'd have said nothing, I'd have thought nothing...
他不斷的對我說他什麼也沒做
...but he goes on and on, running down to me how he ain't been doing nothing...
而且也沒事發生  等等等等
...and nothing's been going on, and all this bullshit.
那時我便知道  這人參與了不法行為
So right then and there I know this cat's got something going down.
而且是大案
Pretty fucking great.
亞拔  你怎麼回事
Albert, what's wrong with you?
你要我來這裏  浪費我的時間
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
你見過坐過牢的人
You saw a guy on the street who's an ex-con?
- 是的  - 那麼我很喜出望外
- That's right. - Well, I am over-fucking-whelmed.
你想為此拿警章嗎
What do you want for that, a Junior G-man badge?
你會查跑車的事嗎
You gonna make the call on them Porsches or what?
他是說笑嗎
Is he kidding me?
我告訴你  滑頭從不說笑
I'm telling you, this Slick is no joke.
他為人緊張
You know what I'm saying?
- 你說什麼  - 什麼
- Say what? Say what? - What?
- 滑頭  那是什麼意思  - 他常叫別人為滑頭
- You said, "Slick". What does that mean? - Slick. That's what he calls people, "Slick".
把他的事告訴我
And tell me about him.
他約六英尺高  有許多監獄的紋身
About 6 feet tall, lot of jailhouse tats.
這兒刺有一頭大孔雀
Got a big-ass peacock right here.
他叫什麼名字
What's his name?
姓查
Cheritto.
查·米高
Michael Cheritto.
自一九七六年起被捕三十三次
33 busts since 1976.
十一次持械行劫  三次給定罪
Eleven for armed robbery, three convictions.
判刑三至五年  在紐約服刑兩年
Two out of a three-to-five-year beef in Attica. Three years in Marion.
中西部服刑三年  因誤殺罪在霍森監獄服刑五年
Five years in Folsom off a knock-back to involuntary manslaughter.
- 他的案底達兩英吋厚  - 很好
- Jacket's 2 inches thick. - Okay.
- 現在還有誰有聽  -  澤加和我  以及舒華茲
- Who do I have there now? - Drucker and me, boss. And Schwartz.
通知特別調查科
Tell SIS I want full surveillance.
我要二十四小時監視他
That's 24 hours. Round the clock, day and night.
不斷監視跟蹤他  監聽他的汽車和房子
We never close. Open seven days a week. Bug the car, the house, the work.
一舉一動
When he moves or sits, like in a restaurant...
和誰人一起也拍照
...I want pictures of who he moves and sits with.
調查他們  若有案底便跟蹤他們
Then run makes on them. They got jackets, I wanna see who they move and sit with.
我要明天便執行
I want it up and running by tomorrow night.
- 把手放在我看得到的地方  - 什麼
- Put your hands where I can see them. - What?
- 把手放在我看得到的地方  - 好的
- Put your hands where I can see them. - All right.
我會告訴你做什麼  以及怎樣去做
I tell you what to do, I tell you how to do it.
現在  只用你的右手  只准右手
Now, with your right hand only, your right hand only...
把包裹拿出來  扔過來
...take the package and throw it in here.
你右面  後面有人
Fuck. Behind you. On the right.
羅傑·宏山
Yeah, Roger Van Zant?
- 你是誰  - 你知道我是誰
- Yeah, who's this? - You know who this is.
我知道
Yes, I do. Yes, I do.
我派人送包裹  他沒來電話  一切妥當吧
I sent a guy to deliver the package. He didn't call. Is everything right?
我告訴你  忘記那筆錢
Tell you what, forget the money.
- 什麼  - 忘記那筆錢
- What? - Forget the money.
呃
Wh...
數目不少  你究竟想做什麼  忘記那筆錢是什麼意思
It's a lot of money. What are you doing? What do you mean, forget the money?
我在做什麼  我在對著話筒自說自話
What am I doing? I'm talking to an empty telephone...
我不明白
I don't understand.
因為電話的另一端是個死人
...because there is a dead man on the other end of this fucking line.
天吶
Oh, my.
- 你喜歡嗎  - 看我的戒指
- Do you like it? - Look at my ring.
真漂亮
Wow.
你知道的嗎
Did you know about this? It's so beautiful.
你瘋了
You are insane.
喜歡嗎
Do you like it?
- 很漂亮  - 是啊  很漂亮
- It's beautiful. - Yeah, it's pretty good.
- 別問他哪兒得來的  - 對  別問
- Just don't ask him where he got it. - Yeah, that's right.
你長大後想做什麼  寶貝
What do you wanna be when you grow up, honey?
我不知道
I don't know.
她不知道  像我一樣  我亦不知道
She doesn't know. Just like me. I don't know either.
你好
Hello?
嗨  是我
Hi, it's me.
我在想你是否會來電話
Hey. I was wondering if you'd call.
我很忙  我能見你嗎
I've been busy. Can I see you?
我害怕那只是一夜情
I was afraid that was just the one night, you know?
對我來說不是
No, not for me, it wasn't.
我也不是
Yeah, me neither.
我能來嗎
Can I fall by?
- 可以  - 好的  一會兒見
- Yeah. - Okay, I'll see you in a little bit.
謝謝
Thank you.
晚安
Good night.
可惡的會議
Goddamn convention.
- 哪一個是滑頭  - 魁梧的那個
- Which one's Slick? - The wide one.
有兩個監視器
Got two transmitters.
分別在防火板及輪內
One's in the wheel well, backup's in the firewall.
是我們的車
Okay, get ready.
- 跟尼爾道別了嗎  - 晚安
- Did you say good night to Neil? - Good night.
金髮的是施基斯  特別調查組已派人跟蹤他
One with the blond hair is Chris Shiherlis. SIS has got a revolving tail...
並監聽了他家的座機
...and hung a wire on the house phone.
查把車三次駛過貴重金屬庫
Cheritto's cruised the precious-metals depository three times.
白金銀和一些金條
Platinum, silver, and some bullion.
森美和我認為是他們下一目標
Sammy and I think that's gonna be their next score.
那獨行者是誰
Who's the loner?
我們第一次見他  還沒開始跟蹤他
First time we're seeing him. We're not on him yet.
立即開始吧
Well, get on it.
好的
Okay.
他們下次做案得手走出大門時
When these guys walk out the door of whatever score they're gonna take next...
一定會大感驚愕
...they're gonna have the surprise of a lifetime.
我要走了
Hey, baby. Time to go.
我令你很開心吧
I showed you a good time, didn't I?
是啊
Oh, yeah.
你很棒  你不錯
You fly. You cool.
你騙我  我看得出別人騙我
You're lying to me. I can always tell when people lie to me.
我沒說謊  你很勇猛
Mm, I ain't lying. You a hot dog.
是出色的騎士
A regular rodeo rider.
是我試過最精彩的性行為
And this was the monster fuck of my young life.
我現在得回到街上去
Now I got to get my ass street side, sugar.
你沒有老實的作風
You don't have a truth-telling style.
- 你說什麼  - 你不知道是什麼回事
- What are you talking about? - You don't know what this is.
是死神來探望你
The Grim Reaper's visiting with you.
你去了哪兒
Where you been?
塘鵝彎的特別收容所
SHU at Pelican Bay.
以及霍森監獄B座
New Folsom, B-wing.
我是一個想做大買賣的人
I am a cowboy looking for anything heavy.
比利說來找你
Billy Ricketts said come see you.
因此我到來
That is why I am here.
你為何不
Why don't you...?
你為何不打電話給這人
Why don't you call this guy?
他經常招人入伙
This guy's always putting guys on.
謝謝  兄弟
Thank you, brother.
- 我要請你喝酒嗎  - 請我喝酒
- I'll buy you a drink? - Buy me a drink.
- 笑什麼  - 沒什麼
- What's so funny? - Nothing.
- 這傢伙  真夠傻的  - 你在責備我嗎
- It's really dumb. - Something smells negligent.
你們天生一對
You two are perfect for each other. How did you meet?
我念小學時認識一人
I knew this guy in, uh, grade school.
他叫羅爾  什麼的
He was named Raoul, uh... Whatever.
他可以把手指彼此屈折起來
Anyway, the guy could take his fingers and fold them over, one over the other.
他可以把眼瞼向外翻
Then he'd turn his eyelids inside out...
我禁不住對你上下其手  是真的
I can't keep my hands off you, and that's the truth.
你吸引人的地方在於你那獸性的方式
That's what's so wonderful about you, in that bestial sort of way.
女人
Woman.
這最好是轟動的大事
This better be earth-shattering.
為羅爾乾杯
That's what she tells us. To Raoul.
- 羅爾  - 敬羅爾
- Raoul. - To Raoul.
我是韓·雲信
Yeah, Vincent Hanna.
發現她時是這樣的
Here's how we found her.
- 她有多大  - 十六七歲
- How old? - Sixteen, seventeen.
在此約六小時
Been here about six hours.
她怎麼死的
How'd she die, Rachel?
頭部遭受重擊  大腦血腫
Beat her head in, same as the others. Cerebral hematoma.
那是誰
Who's that?
- 我猜是死者母親及兄弟  - 他們為何到來
- Mother and siblings, I guess. - What the hell they doing here?
酒店內有人認識死者  就通知了家人
Because it's fucked up. Somebody inside knew the girl and called the family.
讓我看看
Okay, let's go.
不錯
That's nice.
直覺告訴我  化驗精液是同一人
When I run a DNA check on the semen, my intuition says it's coming up the same guy.
是連環謀殺案  要由你著手調查
So it's a series, and ending up in your court.
- 警長有頭緒嗎  - 還沒有
- Sheriff's Homicide getting anywhere? - Not yet.
- 攔住她  - 放開我
- Get her. - Get off me. Get off me.
噢
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
- 天啊  - 冷靜
- Oh, my God. - Hold it, hold it.
- 她在哪兒  - 冷靜
- Where is she? - Easy, easy, easy.
別這樣
Please. Please, come on.
- 沒事的  - 誰幹的
- It's okay. It's okay. - Who did this?
我的女兒呢  她在哪兒
Where's my baby? Where is she?
我要知道是什麼回事
I need to know what happened.
我猜是很轟動吧
I guess the Earth shattered.
你為何不讓博高送你回家
So why didn't you let Bosko take you home?
我不想掃他們的興  有什麼事
I didn't wanna ruin their night too. What was it?
你不想知道的
You don't wanna know.
我想知道你為何扳起臉孔
I'd like to know what's behind that grim look.
我不能透露  你是知道的
I don't do that. You know it. Let's go. Come on.
你從沒告訴我  我會摒諸事外
You never told me I'd be excluded.
我告訴你  我們在一起時  你要和我分享
I told you when we hooked up, baby, that you were gonna have to share me...
世上所有的醜行及醜惡的人
...with all the bad people and all the ugly events on this planet.
我同意接受分享  因為我愛你
And I bought into that sharing because I love you.
即使你發胖  禿頭  沒錢  我仍會愛你
I love you fat, bald, money, no money, driving a bus. I don't care.
但你一定要存在
But you have got to be present like a normal guy some of the time.
那是分享  這不是分享  是殘餘的
That's sharing. This is not sharing, this is leftovers.
明白了  我該回家  然後我該說
Oh, I see. What I should do is come home and say:
寶貝兒  你知道嗎  我今天走進一所房子
Hi, honey, guess what? I walked into this house today...
這癮君子用微波爐煮熟了孩子
...where this junkie asshole just fried his baby in a microwave...
就因為他的哭聲太吵鬧  我和你分享吧
...because it was crying too loud, so let me share that with you.
讓我們分享此事  而在分享時
Come on, let's share that, and in sharing it...
我們會宣洩一切可怕的事件  對嗎
...we'll somehow cathartically dispel all that heinous shit, right?
錯  你知道為什麼嗎
Wrong. You know why?
你喜歡正常的做法
Because you prefer the normal routine.
我們做愛  你不說話
We fuck, then you lose the power of speech.
我得保持我的痛苦
Because I gotta hold on to my angst.
我保存它  因為我需要藉此提高警覺
I preserve it, because I need it. It keeps me sharp, on the edge.
我要這樣做
Where I gotta be.
你不是和我同住
You don't live with me.
你和死者的殘骸同住
You live among the remains of dead people.
你篩選碎片  在地勢找線索
You read the terrain.
你找尋死亡的跡象
You search for signs of passing...
找獵物的氣味
...for the scent of your prey...
然後追捕他們
...and then you hunt them down.
這是你唯一投入的事
That's the only thing you're committed to.
其餘的是你留下的爛攤子
The rest is the mess you leave as you pass through.
我不明白為何不能離開你
What I don't understand is why I can't cut loose of you.
嘿  莉莉安
Hey. Miss Lillian.
走吧  寶貝
Let's go, baby.
我見過經理  那是老闆嗎
I met the manager. Is that the boss?
我為他每天所做的事而坐牢
I did time for what that motherfucker does every day.
你可忍受直至找到新工作嗎
Baby, can you just handle it till we find you something new?
你可以嗎
Can you do that?
更難忍受的我亦捱過
Ain't a hard time been invented that I cannot handle.
你為何和我在一起  莉莉安
What you hanging with me for, Lillian?
因為你令我感驕傲
Because I'm proud of you.
你以我為榮嗎
You're proud of me?
為什麼
What the hell you proud of me for?
回家吧
Come on home.
- 你在哪兒做什麼  - 我滑雪
- What were you doing there? - I was skiing.
我想滑雪
I was trying to ski.
那兒的人會這樣做  去滑雪
That's what people do there. You go skiing...
可結識別人
...and you meet people.
你想開心一下
You try to have a good time.
- 你開心嗎  - 不
- Did you have a good time? - No.
為什麼
Why not?
我不擅交際
I'm not good at meeting people.
你認識了我
You met me.
我沒仔細想  事情便發生了
Well, that happened without my thinking about it.
可能是因為這樣
Which is why, probably.
不  是因為你是個好女人
No, it's because you were fine.
伊荻
Eady.
和我到外地去
Take off with me for a while.
- 去哪兒  - 新西蘭
- Where? - New Zealand.
何時
When?
我不能和你同去  但你可以在那兒與我會和
I have to go separate, but you could meet me there.
但我的工作
But my job, my...
我有錢  你不用工作  你可以在那兒開設計公司
I got money. You don't need money. You could set up a studio, do work there.
- 我不知道  - 還要知道什麼
- I don't know. - What's there to know?
你結婚了嗎
Are you married?
- 什麼  - 你來了又走了
- What? - You come and go...
我才沒有結婚
The last thing I am is married.
我的生活正在走下坡
I'm a needle starting at zero going the other way, a double blank.
可是  突然
Then, all of a sudden...
出現了你這樣的人
...someone like you comes along.
- 你不瞭解我  - 足夠瞭解了
- You don't know me, Neil. - I know enough.
跟我走
Come with me.
有何不妥
What's wrong, baby?
沒什麼  一切妥當  你會去嗎
Nothing's wrong. Everything's right. Will you go?
會
Yeah.
好
Good.
- 嘿  親愛的  - 嗨
- Hey, sweetie. - Hi.
你忘記媽媽會接你嗎
What happened? You forget your mom was picking you up?
不是
No.
怎麼回事
So, what's going on?
我想獨自一人待著
I felt like being alone.
好吧  上車  我送你回家
Okay. Come on, I'll drive you home.
- 嘿  麥克  - 嘿  羅蘭
- Hey, Mike. - Hey, Lauren.
有何動靜
What's happening?
長官
Lieutenant. Sir.
傑克遜警長想知道有何動靜
Captain Jackson wants to know what's going on.
沒動靜  不要用無線電
Nothing's going on. Stay off the air.
傑克遜
Jackson's a...
好技術
Technique.
芝麻開門
Open sesame. Right there.
就是他
There he goes.
- 我們走吧  - 我快完事了
- We walk. - I'm right there.
我們撤  即刻  快點
We walk! Now! Come on.
他聽到了
He's heard it.
他們來了
Heads up.
- 有一個出來了  - 等一等  隊長
- One's coming out. - Hold it, captain.
- 雲信  他沒帶走任何東西  - 是的  我看見了
- Vincent, he's not carrying anything. - Yeah, I see.
- 行動  - 得讓我上司批准
- Here we go. - Not till my boss says so.
雲信  他們沒拿東西
Vincent, both of them are not carrying anything.
- 讓他們走  - 什麼意思
- Okay, let them go. - What do you mean?
我們可以拘捕他們
We can take them...
控以何罪  非法闖入嗎
What are you gonna take them on? Breaking and entry?
他們沒偷東西  明白嗎
They didn't steal anything. Don't you get it?
行為不檢
It gets knocked back to some misdemeanor...
他們坐牢半年便出獄  不行
...they do six months and they're out. No fucking way.
我可不想接受批評  他們不能走
I'm not taking the heat from my boss. They're not walking.
他們會走  今次行動由我指揮
That's exactly what they're gonna do. They're gonna walk. This is my operation.
我的戰略指揮凌駕你的職級
I have tactical command that supersedes your rank.
他們會離去  你會讓他們走
They will walk away and you will let them. Fuck.
繼續工作
Back to work.
洛城警方  密探  警方從何而來
L.A.P.D. Gee, what? Where the fuck did this heat come from?
他們或許知道那兒會被劫
Maybe it's the score they were onto.
但不知道是我們  因為那兒以前曾遇劫
The place, not us. Because it's been hit a couple of times, you know.
假設他們知道我們的電話  住所
Assume they got our phones, assume they got our houses...
知道我們在此集會
...assume they got us right here, right now as we sit.
假設他們知道一切
Everything. Assume it all.
我們如何付劫銀行的上期
How we gonna buy the bank package from Kelso?
- 我先墊付吧  - 宏山呢
- I'll front that. That's not a problem. - What happens to Van Zant?
警方現在正追查我們  你想和他開戰嗎
With the heat we got, do you wanna play World War II in the streets with Van Zant?
不  我想拿七十五萬
No, I want my 750. And he gets a pass?
我比你更想殺了宏山  他太放肆了
I got more motivation to whack Van Zant than either of you. He is a fucking luxury.
問題是  我們劫銀行  還是離去
Our problem is, take the bank or split right now?
不要回家收拾東西
Do not go home, do not pack, nothing.
三十秒後我們會各走各路
Thirty seconds flat from now, we are gone on our separate ways.
就這樣
That's it.
基斯
Chris.
值得冒險劫銀行
The bank is worth the risk.
我需要錢
I need it, brother.
我認為我們該留下來劫銀行
We should stay and take it down. That's where I come out.
你做什麼我亦跟隨
I roll with you, Neil. Whatever. Whatever.
但今次不行  米高  你要自行決定
No, not on this one, Michael. On this one, you're on your own.
這是最好的做法嗎
You figure this is the best thing to do?
是最好的做法嗎
This is the best thing to do?
事後我有打算  值得為這筆錢坐牢
I got plans. I'm going away after. So for me the reward is maybe worth the stretch.
但綺玲很照顧你  你有許多錢
But Elaine takes good care of you. You got plenty put away.
你有物業
You got T-bonds, real estate.
若我是你  便不參與今次行動
If I were you, I would be smart. I would cut loose of this.
對我來說  行動使生活更刺激
Well, you know, for me, the action is the juice.
我參加
I'm in.
你呢
You too?
我會
Yeah, sure.
動手吧
Let's go.
去他們的  行動吧
Fuck them, let's do it.
那好  我們有許多事要做
All right, let's go. We got a lot of work to do.
- 你們不能進去  - 查查這個
- You can't go in there. - Watch this.
- 抱歉  等等  - 提姆  我回頭再給你打電話
- Excuse me. That... - Tim, I gotta call you back.
你得提前預約
You have to have an appointment.
- 我能幫助你嗎  - 你是馬·亞倫嗎
- Can I help you? - Are you Alan Marciano?
- 是我  你他媽是誰  - 我是誰
- Yeah, and who the fuck are you? - Who am I?
- 嘿  - 洛城警局的韓·雲信探長
- Hey. Hey. - Lieutenant Vincent Hanna, L.A.P.D.
這裏是賭城拉斯維加斯  不在你的管轄範圍
L.A.? This is Las Vegas. You don't even have jurisdiction here.
你知道在惹惱誰嗎
Hey. Hey, I don't know who the fuck you guys think you're pushing around...
- 我認識這兒的大人物  - 我可以讓賭城警方拘押你
- ...but I know people here, okay? - Las Vegas P.D. takes you into custody.
你會因從北卡羅來納走私香煙
You are extradited to Newark on a New Jersey warrant...
而被引渡回紐華克
...for smuggling cigarettes up from North Carolina three years ago...
或是你可和我們合作
...or you go to work for us.
簡單明快
Cut and dried.
- 就是這樣  - 媽的
- That is it. - Oh, shit.
施·莎蓮
Charlene Shiherlis.
- 誰  - 誰
- Who? - Who?
誰  你是貓頭鷹嗎
Who? What are you, a fucking owl?
和你在電話中淫聲浪語的女子
The lady you been talking dirty to on the telephone every day the last week.
你不能把她和我扯上了
Yeah, you know what? You can't tie me to her.
你肯定會回去新澤西的  笨蛋
Who needs to? Your ass is on a plane back to New Jersey, jack off.
我為何會勾搭上那個婊子呢
Oh, man, I just... Why did I get mixed up with that bitch?
因為她的屁股很誘人
Because she got a great ass!
你不知自己在做什麼
And you got your head all the way up it.
天啊
Jesus.
我很兇  是嗎  當我想起屁股  女人的屁股
When I think of asses, a woman's ass...
便想起一些東西
...something comes out of me.
- 那麼  - 不要你說太多
- So? - So no big thing.
我只想知道她丈夫和他那夥人
All I want is her husband and his whole fucking crew.
你會和澤加合作
Now, you're gonna work with Sergeant Drucker here.
聖金文路和赫摩撒街
San Clemente Road and Hermosa.
我們在那兒穿過欄柵
That's where we cut through the fence. That's the access.
對
Right.
保安系統不堪一擊
The security systems around here are a joke.
逃走路線一是聖雲遜湯瑪士橋
St. Vincent Thomas Bridge, that's Escape Route Number 1.
路線二  是安納咸公路往一一零號公路
Number 2, over here, Anaheim to the 110.
- 好  - 好嗎
- Good. - Okay?
- 很好  - 明白嗎  好的  走吧
- Yeah. That's fine. - Got it? Good. Let's go.
他們回頭望向
They were looking back...
這方向
...in this direction.
貨櫃設施
A container facility?
- 什麼  - 太明顯了  對他們來說得益太少了
- For a cartage theft? - Too visible. Too lowball for them.
有煉油廠和廢車場
Next door's an oil refinery, over there's a scrap yard.
煉油廠發薪用支票  沒有現金  廢車場亦一樣
Refinery only pays by check. No cash around. Same for the scrap yard.
也許他們要偷車輪蓋
Maybe they're stealing hubcaps.
煉油廠和廢車場
A refinery and a scrap yard.
- 是什麼回事  - 我們正想知道
- What the hell is going on? - That's what we're trying to figure out.
我們以為很清楚
We thought we had it.
這下倒糊塗了
Thought we had it.
我知道他們在看些什麼
I got an idea of what they were looking at.
- 你們想知道嗎  - 是什麼
- You wanna know what they're looking at? - What?
這人真了不起  他真行
I mean, is this guy something, or is he something?
這夥人很棒
This crew is good.
你們想知道嗎
You know what they were looking at?
是什麼
What?
是我們
Us.
洛城警局
The L.A.P.D.
是警局
The police department.
我們給人認出了
We just got made.
是的
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
好吧  雜種
Okay, motherfucker!
祈素交出來了嗎
Kelso come through?
交出來了  藍圖很詳盡
Yeah, you can build a bank with these.
那人姓韓  名雲信
Name is Hanna. First name Vincent.
我用五百元賄賂這警員  韓監視你一舉一動
I smeared this sergeant in Vice five yards. Hanna's all over you.
監視所有的車  米高及施的家
He's on all the work cars. Michael's house, Shiherlis'.
沒監視你  不知你晚上在哪兒
Not yours, they've been losing you at night.
他很積極  他畢業後加入陸戰隊
Hanna's a hot dog. Graduate school. Marine Corps.
是劫案及兇殺組探長
Lieutenant, Robbery-Homicide, Major Crime Unit.
拘捕過不少人  在芝加哥殺了法蘭
He's taken down some heavy crews. Blew away Frankie Yonder in Chicago.
法蘭是個狂人
And he was a fucking maniac.
他之前在毒品科工作  離婚兩次
He was working Narcotics before that. Had some problems, divorced twice.
目前的太太叫彩鈿  是他鼓動嚴密監視的
Current wife's Justine. He's why the extra heat.
罪案科警官
The Vice sergeant...
說韓喜歡你
...says Hanna likes you.
認為你是明星  行事很有技巧
Thinks you're some kind of star. You do this sharp, you do that sharp.
他能想到這樣看他有多聰明
Look how sharp this guy is to figure that.
他像心臟病般好笑  三次婚姻
Funny as a heart attack, man. Three marriages.
你認為他喜歡待在家嗎
What the fuck do you think that means? He likes staying home?
他是那種
Means the man is one of those guys out there...
整晚工作的人  很投入
...prowling around all night, dedicated.
有他和警方監視  取消劫銀行吧
With this guy and this much heat, you should pass.
值得冒險一試
It's worth the stretch.
這人是否能抓住罪犯都無所謂  可你輸不起
This guy can hit and miss. You can't miss once.
你肯定嗎
You sure?
肯定
I'm sure.
我們去車房吧
Let's go to the garage.
彩鈿
Justine.
Justine?
我們要去哪兒
Where we going?
- 好吧  你要去哪兒  - 外面
- Okay, where are you going? - Out.
- 他們用什麼頻道  - 九號戰術頻道
- What are you on? - TAC 9.
他們在四零五號公路  往機場方向北走
They're northbound out LAX on the 405. We got four ground units.
我是十八號機的韓·雲信  誰和我合作
This is Vincent Hanna in Air 18. Who have I got?
我是四十號機的JJ  高·裏察和我在一起
Hey, Vincent, it's JJ. I'm in Air 40. Richard Glover's with me.
車在一零五號公路  東行接近一一零號公路
It's on the 105 eastbound approaching the 110 interchange.
- 是交替追蹤嗎  - 是的  前面有兩輛車  三輛在他後面
- You running a revolving tail? - Yeah, I got two units in front, three behind.
要其中一輛在維蒙街接我
Okay, have one of them pick me up at the Vermont on-ramp.
走吧
Let's go.
我離他有一百碼嗎   太近還是太遠
Am I 100 yards, or what? Am I close or far, or what?
離他三百碼  在中央行車線
Three hundred yards, center lane.
你好嗎
How you doing?
我請你喝咖啡如何
What do you say I buy you a cup of coffee?
- 好的  走吧  - 跟著我
- Yeah, sure. Let's go. - Follow me.
你在霍森監獄七年
Seven years in Folsom.
單獨囚禁三年
In the hole for three.
之前在麥尼爾監獄
McNeil before that.
那兒是一如所說的那麼兇殘嗎
McNeil as tough as they say?
你想成為監獄學者嗎
You looking to become a penologist?
你想再坐牢嗎
You're looking to go back?
我追捕過不少把事情搞砸  只能束手被擒的人
You know, I chase down some crews guys just looking to fuck up,
再次送回監獄  你是那種人嗎
get busted back. That you?
你拘捕的一定是飯桶笨蛋
You must've worked some dipshit crews.
我拘捕各式各樣的人
I worked all kinds.
你幻想我身上有刺青
You see me doing thrill-seeking liquor-store holdups...
行劫酒鋪嗎
...with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
- 不  我不會的  - 對
- No, I do not. - Right.
我不會再坐牢
I am never going back.
那麼便別再行劫
Then don't take down scores.
我做擅長做的事  我行劫
I do what I do best, I take scores.
你做擅長的事  阻止我
You do what you do best, trying to stop guys like me.
你從不想過正常生活
So you never wanted a regular-type life?
是怎樣的  燒烤和踢足球嗎
What the fuck is that? Barbecues and ball games?
是的
Yeah.
- 你的生活正常嗎  - 我的生活  不  我的生活
- This regular-type life like your life? - My life? No, my life...
一塌糊塗
No, my life's a disaster zone.
我的繼女情緒深受困擾
I got a stepdaughter so fucked up...
因為她的生父是個大混蛋
...because her real father is this large-type asshole.
我有太太  我的婚姻正頻臨破碎邊緣
I got a wife. We're passing each other on the down slope of a marriage...
第三次了
...my third...
因為我常花時間追捕你這樣的人
...because I spend all my time chasing guys like you around the block.
那是我的生活
That's my life.
有人曾對我說
A guy told me one time:
若你感到附近有警方監視
Don't let yourself get attached to anything...
便不能沾上任何不能脫身的事
...you are not willing to walk out on in 30 seconds flat...
三十秒內  一走了之
...if you feel the heat around the corner.
你想捉我  我行動時你亦行動
Now, if you're on me, and you gotta move when I move...
你如何能維持婚姻呢
...how do you expect to keep a marriage?
這說法很有趣
Well, that's an interesting point.
你是僧侶嗎
What are you, a monk?
我有女伴
I have a woman.
你怎麼對她說
What do you tell her?
我告訴她  我是推銷員
I tell her I'm a salesman.
那麼若你見我從街角走來
So then, if you spot me coming around that corner...
你會離開她嗎
...you're just gonna walk out on this woman?
不辭而別
Not say goodbye?
那是自律
That's the discipline.
那很空泛
That's pretty vacant, no?
正是如此
Yeah, it is what it is.
不這樣做  我們還是另找職業吧
It's that, or we both better go do something else, pal.
我不懂做別的
I don't know how to do anything else.
我也不懂
Neither do I.
- 我不想做其他事  - 我也不想
- I don't much want to either. - Neither do I.
我不斷重複這夢境
You know, I have this recurring dream.
我坐在偌大的餐宴席上
I'm sitting at this big banquet table...
我調查的兇案受害人均出席
...and all the victims of all the murders I ever worked are sitting at this table...
他們用黑色的眼珠子瞪望我
...and they're staring at me with these black eyeballs...
因為他們頭部中槍而出血
...because they got eight-ball hemorrhages from the head wounds.
這些發脹的屍體在那兒
And there they are, these big balloon people...
因為他們被殺兩周後才在床下發現
...because I found them two weeks after they'd been under the bed.
鄰居報稱有惡臭
The neighbors reported the smell...
他們均有出席  所有人坐在那兒
...and there they are, all of them just sitting there.
他們說什麼
What do they say?
沒說話
Nothing.
- 沒人說話嗎  - 沒有
- No talk? - None.
他們無話可說
Just... They don't have anything to say.
我們彼此望著對方
See, we just look at each other.
他們望著我  就是這樣  夢境是這樣
They look at me. And that's it, that's the dream.
我夢過自己溺水
I have one where I'm drowning.
我得弄醒自己  開始呼吸  否則會死
And I gotta wake myself up and start breathing, or I'll die in my sleep.
你知道這象徵著什麼嗎
You know what that's about?
知道  有足夠的時間
Yeah. Having enough time.
- 有足夠的時間做你想做的事嗎  - 是的
- Enough time to do what you wanna do? - That's right.
- 你正在這樣做嗎  - 還沒有
- You doing it now? - No, not yet.
我們坐在這裏
You know, we're sitting here...
一如常人
...you and I, like a couple of regular fellows.
彼此做有需要的事
You do what you do, and I do what I gotta do.
現在我們見過面
And now that we've been face to face...
若我要在案發現場殺你  我會不喜歡的
...if I'm there and I gotta put you away, I won't like it.
但是
But I'll tell you...
若在你和
...if it's between you and some poor bastard...
被你殺死的人當中作選擇
...whose wife you're gonna turn into a widow...
兄弟  沒命的會是你
...brother, you are going down.
我有反面的看法
There's a flip side to that coin.
若你真的使我走投無路  而我要殺你呢
What if you do got me boxed in and I gotta put you down?
因為無論如何  你是無法阻止我的
Because no matter what, you will not get in my way.
是的  我們見過面
We've been face to face, yeah...
但我會毫不猶疑殺你  一秒也不遲疑
...but I will not hesitate. Not for a second.
也許會這樣
Maybe that's the way it'll be.
或是誰曉得呢
Or who knows?
也許我們會永遠不再見
Or maybe we'll never see each other again.
他們擺脫了我們
They dumped us.
什麼
What?
- 他們逃脫了  - 什麼意思
- They dumped us. - What do you mean, they dumped us?
基斯甩掉了跟蹤他的探員
Chris slipped his tail.
他沒跟莎蓮談及買賣的事
He doesn't talk about scores with Charlene...
我無從向馬·亞倫套取資料
...so there's nothing for me to get from Marciano. I tried.
- 查·米高呢  - 亦一樣
- What about Cheritto? - Same.
異頻收發器放在公共汽車上
Transponders got put on a bus to San Clemente.
- 他們擺脫我們所有的監視了嗎  - 是的  同一時間  晚上九時
- They dumped all our surveillance? - Yeah, at the same time. 9 p.m.
我半小時前和麥·尼爾喝咖啡
I had coffee with McCauley half an hour ago!
之後他駛往機場
We were on you. Then McCauley drives into LAX...
我們便無法飛去
...where surveillance can't fly over because of flight paths.
他的車仍在那兒  但人走了
His car's still there. He's gone.
有誰知道他們在哪兒嗎
Does anybody have any idea where the fuck these people are?
他有聯絡嗎
You hear from him yet?
沒有  這令我不安  他在哪兒
Not a thing. And not hearing bothers me more. Where's this guy?
這人  我們僱用他  他說認識麥·尼爾
This guy here. We put him on. Says he knows McCauley.
你是誰
Who are you?
榮谷  我叫榮谷
Waingro. My name's Waingro.
我等他電話  你很熟識他嗎
I've been living in this office day and night. How well do you know him?
我們一起做過不少大買賣
Oh, we took some major scores together.
他為何沒找我
How come I haven't heard from him?
他可能忙著  但他行事很徹底
Well, he's probably busy right now, but he's real thorough.
- 他不會忘記你的  - 噢  那真令人安心
- He ain't gonna forget about you. - Oh, that's reassuring.
我可在這兒出了力
Well, I got some moves I could make here.
可能對你會很有幫助
Probably be a big help to you.
認得那烤肉的人嗎
You recognize the grill man?
- 不認識  - 霍森監獄  D座的  和杜比同一囚室
- No. - Folsom. D-block. Housed with Dobie Rush.
- 我還沒有小休  - 薜哥和彭曹沒上班
- Ain't got my break yet, man. - Cisco and Pancho didn't show.
扔垃圾  到餐廳後抹地
Haul out the garbage. Mop up the back.
稍後再休息吧
Take your break later.
人渣  端菜
Piece of shit. Pick up.
他在哪兒
Where the hell is he?
- 我查看車場  看車是否仍在那兒  - 我也去
- I wanted to check the slot for a work car. - So did I.
是我
Yeah?
等一等
Hang on.
- 喂  - 嘿
- Yeah. - Hey.
用普通電話  撥號103-7206
Use a landline. Call me at 103-7206.
好的
All right.
- 你在哪兒  - 到處有警察監視我
- Where are you? - There's cops all over me, man.
我無法擺脫他們
They're on me like a cheap suit. I can't dump them.
- 他們知道你發現他們了嗎  - 不  沒有  他們平衡緊帖我
- After the fact you spotted them? - No, no. They're doing parallels.
我再試試擺脫他們
I can try to dump them again.
我怎麼知道你是否擺脫了  你會引他們過來找到我們
How are we gonna know if you did? If you didn't, you'll draw them to us.
到宏杜拿去  引開他們
Head for Ventura. Pull them out of here.
好的  對不起  我真不想讓你失望
All right. Hey, I'm sorry, man. Last thing I wanna do is let you down.
快點
Come on, man.
端出去
Pick up.
- 嘿  尼爾  你好嗎  - 你好嗎  兄弟
- Hey, hey, Neil, man. What up? - What's up, brother?
你在這兒做什麼
Man, what you doing here?
我在找能夠應付警方追蹤的司機
What I am doing is I'm looking for a driver who can handle scanners and a radio.
現在便要
Right now, today.
你還記得嗎
You remember the drill?
記得
Yeah, man, sure.
你可靠嗎
You cool?
你知道我很可靠
Oh, man, now, you know I'm cool.
你現在便答覆我  肯或不肯
One answer, yes or no. Right now.
好的  去它的  我答應
Yeah, man. Fuck, yeah. You're on.
五分鐘後到後面來
Out back in five.
- 是什麼燒焦了  - 不是我幹的
- What's burning? What's burning? - Nothing I'm doing.
是什麼事
What is this?
你要去哪兒
Where do you think you're going?
剛好超過第一版的康丁斯基的色彩理論
Just came across a first edition of Kandinsky's Theory of Color.
是啊  情況很好
Yeah. No, it's in good condition.
這艘船沒有停下  也沒有回覆警方的喊話
And it will not stop or answer radio communication.
編號為一八零的這艘船被稱為金銀一號
The 180-foot vessel is called Jin Yin Number 1...
涉嫌偷渡中國非法移民
...and is suspected of smuggling Chinese illegal aliens.
警方的巡邏機於星期六發現了這艘可疑船隻
It was spotted Saturday by patrol aircraft.
- 趴下  - 別動  不許動
- Stay down. - Don't move! Don't fucking move!
舉起手來  舉起你們的雙手
Put your hands in the air! Put your hands in the air! Put them up!
趴下  兩腿著地
Down, down! Get on your knees.
- 把鑰匙給我  - 跪下
- Give me the keys. - Get on your knees.
跪下
Get on your knees!
過去那邊  趴下
Hey. Hey! Get over there. Get the fuck... Get down.
轉身  把手放在背後
Turn around! Put your hands behind you. Behind you!
趴下
Get down! Stay down!
趴下  混蛋
Get down! Get down! Down, you stupid son of a...
- 趴下  - 拿鎖匙來
- Down! Down, now! - Keys! Keys! Keys!
別動
All of you stay down.
我們不想傷人  只要銀行的錢  不是你們的錢
We want to hurt no one. We're here for the bank's money, not your money.
你們不會損失  政府購買了保險
Your money's insured. You're not gonna lose a dime.
想想你的家人  別冒生命危險  別逞能
Think of your families. Don't risk your life. Don't try and be a hero.
我要你們都坐在地上  手放在頭上
Right now I want you to sit on the floor and put your hands on your head.
如果感到不舒服或著心臟難受  便靠在牆上
Anybody feels sick, anybody got heart trouble, go ahead and lean against the wall.
- 給我鎖匙  - 什麼鎖匙
- Give me the key. - What key?
坐下  別動
Get down and stay down!
坐著別動  讓傷口流血吧
Sit there. Sit there. Don't move. Let it bleed.
趴下
Get down!
嘿
Hey. Hey!
把頭低下
Put your head down.
- 再看我一眼  我就殺了你  - 趴下
- Look at me again, I'll kill you. - Stay down. Down.
- 把頭低下  - 低頭  低頭
- Put your head down! - Get down. Get down.
- 嘿  卡索斯  - 怎麼啦
- Hey, Casals. - Yeah.
你們在調查麥·尼爾的案子吧
You guys working a case on a Neil McCauley?
機密線人許·班尼打來電話  說了關於搶劫銀行的事
This CI, Hugh Benny, called in about a bank they're looking at or something.
雲信
Vincent.
早上十一時半  遠東國家銀行
Far East National Bank, 11:30!
在第五街交界設路障
I want a block at Figueroa and 5th...
花街及第六界北行亦設路障
...and I want a block northbound Flower at 6th.
他們出來了
They're already coming out.
好的  要在車上捉他們  等他們全上車後再動手
Okay, we're gonna have to take them in the car. Wait till they are all in.
要利落地射殺他們  別傷及無辜
Get clean shots. Watch your background.
- 警察  走開  - 怎麼回事
- Police! Move! - What's going on?
閃開  趴下
Move. Move. Get down.
小心
Look out.
- 讓開  - 洛城警局  趴下
- Move it, come on. - L.A.P.D. Get down.
走開  趴下
Move it. Down, down, down.
我們成功了  尼爾
We did it, right, Neil? Huh?
走開
Move!
趴下
Get down.
該死
Fuck. Fuck!
開車
In the car!
走
Go! Go! Go!
- 混賬東西  - 快走
- Son of a bitch! - Go, go!
走
Go!
快走
快起來  走
Come on. Come on.
帶他離開這兒
Get him out of here.
趴下
Get down! Now!
見鬼
Shit.
離開這兒  快趴下
Out of the way! Down! Out of the way! Get them down! Now, now!
離開這兒
No, out of the way. Out of the way.
媽咪  媽咪
Mommy? Mommy!
過來  寶貝
Come here, honey.
來吧  孩子
Come on, honey.
我抱著你  沒事兒了
I got you. It's okay now.
今天發生慘劇  銀行劫案禍延街頭
Tragedy in a Southland neighborhood today. A bank robbery spilled out into the street.
鈕·歌迪現時在現場作最新報導
Claudia Newman, live on the scene. She has the latest. Claudia?
今天下午  搶劫銀行未遂使這兒很可怕
This afternoon, this neighborhood was terrorized by a bank holdup gone wrong.
街上滿是行人和孩子  警方和武裝劫匪激烈交火
With the streets full of mid-day shoppers and kids, police and armed robbers...
- 勞駕  酒保  - 這就來  女士
- Excuse me, bartender? - One minute, lady.
新聞提要  劫匪逃走終於死亡
...robbery, pursuit and, finally, death.
銀行劫案震動洛杉磯地區
A Los Angeles neighborhood is shaken by a bank robbery...
最後以兇殺及恐懼告終
...that ended in homicide and terror.
查·米高是四名劫匪之一
One suspect, Michael Cheritto, is one of four men involved in the foiled robbery.
- 他在現場死去  - 喝點什麼  小姐
- He died at the scene. - What can I get you, miss?
另一個受重傷的疑匪  當·畢頓
Also fatally wounded, suspect Donald Breedan...
小姐
Miss?
在警方和劫匪交火時  中槍身亡
...during the extensive gunfire between police and suspects.
好了  按著他
All right, hold him. Hold him.
- 沒事兒的  - 沒事兒了
- All right. All right. - It's all right.
- 情況怎樣  - 他失血過多  驚嚇過度
- So? - Well, he's got blood loss and shock.
我給你最少量的嗎啡止痛
I'm gonna give you quarter-grain morphine for the pain. Subcutaneous injection.
告訴我吧
Bottom line.
主要是組織受損  那是好事  他的鎖骨折斷
It's mostly tissue damage, which is good, but his clavicle's fractured.
- 能讓他休息嗎  - 六七個小時
- Can he rest for a while? - Six, seven hours.
- 不能多留嗎  - 不能
- That's it? - That's it.
- 脫下你的襯衣  - 什麼
- Take off your shirt. - What?
脫下你的襯衣
Take off your shirt.
這是女兒在父親節送給我的
My... Look, my daughter gave it to me for Father's Day.
我不管  脫下來
I don't give a shit who gave it to you. Take it off.
基斯  嘿
Chris. Hey.
聽著
Chris, listen to me.
奈德會接你  送你到他家中
Nate's gonna pick you up. He's gonna take you to his place.
- 莎蓮呢  - 我們得離開這兒
- Where's Charlene? - We gotta get out of here.
新聞一直在播銀行的事
We're all over the 6:00 news.
- 我們必須得走  - 沒有她我不走
- We gotta get out of here. - I'm not going without her.
你考慮一下  在奈德那兒見
Think about that. I will meet you at Nate's.
你去哪兒
Where are you going?
查探逃走路線是否給洩露了
I gotta find out if our out got spilled along with every other damn thing.
是誰告密的
Who did it?
有誰沒參加
Who wasn't there?
齊祖
Trejo.
在奈德家見
I'll see you at Nate's.
- 是的  - 你仍想要我嗎
- Yeah. - Yeah. You still want me?
你來這裏接我和多明吧
You come down here right now and you get me. Dominick and me. Okay?
好的  寶貝  我兩小時後到
Okay, baby, okay. I'll be there in two hours, all right?
- 好嗎  - 好吧
- Okay? - All right.
你真該死  基斯  你真該死
Goddamn you, Chris. Goddamn you.
- 你坐飛機前往洛杉磯  - 太好了
- You're on a plane for Los Angeles. - Great.
你為何這樣做  怎麼回事
Why'd you do it? What happened?
- 他們逼迫我  - 誰
- They made me. - Who?
安娜呢
Where's Anna?
她死了
She's dead.
米高和代替你的畢頓亦死了
So is Michael and Breedan, the guy who stood in for you.
- 誰迫害你的  是誰 -  他們威脅安娜
- Who did it? Who did it? - They had Anna, man.
誰威脅她
Who had her?
榮谷
Waingro.
他一個人嗎
On his own?
- 替人賣命  - 誰
- For someone. - Who?
他替別人工作
The other he worked for.
宏山
Zant.
- 宏山  - 對
- Van Zant? - Yeah.
宏山
Van Zant.
- 你肯定嗎  - 宏山
- Are you sure? - Van Zant.
你有說出我們怎樣逃走嗎
Did you say anything about how we're getting out?
- 我認為沒有  - 說吧
- I don't think so, Neil. - Come on.
我不記得了
I don't remember, Neil.
- 我通知救護員  - 我無法活下去的
- I'll call a medic. - I'm not gonna make it.
我全無感覺
I can't feel nothing.
我的安娜死了
My Anna's gone.
她死了
She's gone.
別這樣扔下我  尼爾  求求你  朋友
Don't leave me like this, Neil. Please, holmes.
別這樣扔下我
Don't leave me like this.
- 喂  - 奈德
- Yeah? - Nate.
你用無線電話嗎  用普通電話
You on a cellular? Use a hard line.
這是新的電話
It's a new one.
他住在安僊奴區山景台
The guy lives on Hillside Terrace, Encino.
- 一零七二五號  - 一零七二五號  好的
- 10725. - 10725, okay.
- 基斯呢  - 他和我一起在我家中
- Chris? - He's with me, at my place.
跟著查出榮谷在哪兒
Next, Waingro, okay?
你有時間嗎
You got the time?
我會抽空的  我需要新的逃走路線
I'll make time, and I need a new out laid on.
你怎麼知道被洩露了呢
How do you know it's blown?
我怎麼能相信沒洩露呢
How can I trust it?
好的  沒問題
Okay, you got it.
保住性命
Stay healthy.
莎蓮
Charlene Shiherlis.
澤加在威尼斯區有地方收藏她
Drucker's got a safe house in Venice to stash her in.
尼爾的逃走方法
Our Neil's transportation. When we're done here, get on the phone.
正有人替他安排一切
Somewhere, someone's trying to put it together for him.
你不會認為他已經有計劃了吧
You don't believe McCauley already had a getaway?
他當然有計劃  但他需要另一個計劃  換成你還能相信原來的計劃嗎
Sure he did. Now he needs another one. Would you trust yours after this afternoon?
這告密的混蛋  哪兒找到他的
This rat motherfucker, where did we get him?
他是機密線人  通報劫銀行線索
He's a CI for a burglary cop. Called in the tip on the bank.
談談麥·尼爾吧  還有多少時間
On Neil McCauley, how much time we got?
他有八至十小時安排新逃走路線  之後  他就走了
Eight, 10 hours for him to set up a new out. After that, he's gone.
拜拜了
Bye-bye. Bam.
你向我們告發麥·尼爾  你怎麼知道  誰告訴你的
You ratted McCauley to us. How'd you know? Who told you?
是誰告訴你的  混蛋
Who told you, you rat motherfucker?
是誰
Who?
康尼回來阻擊墨菲  墨菲在奮力拼搶
Connelly back in for Murphy. Murphy with Leggat right there with him.
得球後  準備打門
Murphy tees it up behind the net...
米勒也衝到了前場
...Miller out front. Now here's Murphy with the referee...
榮谷在哪兒
Waingro, where is he?
- 在哪兒  - 我怎麼知道
- Where is he? - How the hell would I know?
嗯  這兒有些什麼
Well, what do we have here, hmm?
這兒漂亮嗎  漂亮嗎
Isn't this pretty? It's pretty.
- 你這個小人  - 你告訴我想脫離目前的困境
- You slimy piece of shit. - You told me you wanted out from under.
你想脫身嗎  這是出路
You're scared to death, right? You want out? This is out, Charlene.
- 你得到什麼好處啦  - 我沒好處  你這個蠢娘們
- Yeah, what's your end? - I... You stupid broad.
- 我怎麼會牽涉此事的  - 嘿  冷靜  別衝動
- How'd I get into this? - Hey, hey, hey. Easy.
你聽到我說的了
You heard me.
她已經夠難受的了  你為何不給她倒杯酒呢
She had a rough ride. Why don't you fix her a drink or something?
- 到櫥櫃看看  - 去她的
- Look in the cabinet above the sink. - Fuck her.
- 你最好進去  不要出來  - 好吧
- You'd better get in there and stay in there. - All right, all right.
看看這兒
Well, lookie here.
我是澤加  洛城警局  兇殺組探員
My name is Sergeant Drucker, L.A.P.D. Homicide.
- 要送多明進睡房嗎  - 他和我待在一起
- You wanna put Dominick in the bedroom? - He stays with me.
坐下
There we go.
現在怎麼辦
So, what now?
他說得對  你想脫身  這是出路
Well, he's right, because you want out, this is out.
- 你真的要出賣基斯嗎  - 正是
- You believe you have to betray Chris. - No shit.
這就對了  你是得這樣做
That's right. You would have to.
若不出賣基斯  多明會是受害人
See, if you don't betray Chris, you victimize Dominick.
因為當你入獄時  他便會成為孤兒
Because he becomes an orphan when you go to prison as an accessory...
你也沒有父母來照顧他
...because you got no living parents to take him.
他會被送進收養所  青少年中心
So he ends up state-raised in foster homes, juvenile facilities.
之後他會偷車
Then he steals a car.
然後入獄學會做真正的罪犯
Then he winds up in gladiator academies like Chino and Tracy.
毀了一生
Fucked for life.
你是過來人  知道會有何下場
You know what happens, because you've been there.
多明沒機會選擇生活  但基斯有
Dominick didn't get a chance yet to choose his life, but Chris did.
你若供出基斯  你會沒有案底
If you give up Chris, you get off clean.
你可以為了孩子而這樣做  你可以撫養他
You can do it for your kid, so you can raise him.
- 你還有什麼條件  - 各種各樣的東西
- What else are you selling? - All kinds of shit.
但我不用說服你  因為我是對的
But I don't have to sell this and you know it, because this kind of shit here sells itself.
最新消息
Okay, Danny, here's an update.
- 澤加在二線  - 等一等
- Drucker's on Line 2. - Lieutenant, hold on for a second.
澤加在另一電話線
Lieutenant, I have Drucker on the other line.
三人通話吧
Oh, well, conference him in.
- 說吧  - 雲信  是我
- Go ahead. - Vincent, it's me.
你的答覆是怎樣的
I want an answer. What's it gonna be?
我們準備好了  她會打電話
We're set here. She'll make the call.
好的  情況是這樣
Okay, that's good. Here's the deal here.
許·班尼已改過自新  成為洗心革面的好市民
Hugh Benny has reformed his wayward life and become a born-again good citizen.
叫榮谷的人向我們出賣了尼爾
Apparently, Neil got sold out to us by this cowboy named Waingro.
榮谷曾是他手下
Waingro used to be a part of Neil's crew...
後替洗錢人工作  他叫宏山
...then he went to work for a money launderer named Van Zant.
現時正派人前住宏山家中  因為他今晚較早前被殺
Units are at Van Zant's house as we speak because he got shot dead earlier tonight.
尼爾要對付的人會是榮谷
Now, if Neil goes after anybody else, it's gonna be Waingro.
榮谷正入住侯爵機場酒店套房
Waingro just got himself a suite at the airport Marquis...
並化名詹美臣  他正在那兒
...under the name "Jameson". He's there now.
我要你把這消息告訴外圍帶家
I want you to get that to bail bondsmen, bookies...
奉派警員及線人
...assignment officers and snitches in County.
任何能把消息外洩的人
Anyone you can think of who'll put it on the street.
派人到酒店駐守  並每隔半小時收聽無線電
Deploy a team at the hotel and personally check their come every 30 minutes.
也許尼爾會殺他  明白嗎  你感覺怎麼樣
Because maybe Neil will go for him. Okay? How you feeling?
- 不算太慘  我會活著  - 很好
- Banged up, but I'll live. - Okay.
他仍在
He's here.
尼爾還沒走
Neil is still here.
我能感覺到
I can feel it.
會留多久
But for how long?
最多七八個小時
Seven, eight hours, max.
你做過什麼
What did you do?
- 是你做的嗎  - 我不是賣金屬的
- That was you? - It's what I don't do, I don't sell metal.
計劃原本順利  但現在出了麻煩
Would have been okay, you fly out after. Now it's jammed.
- 我們要一起走  - 那些人和你一起的嗎
- Now we gotta go together. - Those other people were with you?
我的朋友米高
My friend, Michael...
他知道所冒的險
...he knew the risks. He didn't have to be there.
身處險境便要冒生命危險
It rains, you get wet.
收拾東西
Get packed and let's go.
伊荻
Eady.
你為何這樣對我
Why did you do this to me?
你究竟是誰
Who are you?
不會有事的  明白嗎
It's gonna be all right. You understand? It'll be all right.
不會有事的
It's gonna be all right.
不會的
Right.
這個地址  D層十八單位  有一輛汽車
There's this Camaro at this address, Level D, Slot 18.
這兒有現金
Here's some cash.
此事何時瞭解
When's it over?
二十二小時後
22 hours from now.
- 那時我們便可脫身  - 那時你會讓我離開嗎
- Then we get out of here clean. - When will you let me leave?
那現在就走吧  你想離開嗎  門在那邊
Go now. You want out? There's the door.
你稍後會讓我離開嗎
Will you let me leave later?
情況會不同
It will be different.
你還不明白嗎
Do you understand?
準備好了
It's ready.
雲信
Vincent.
這是我的朋友洛夫
This is my friend Ralph.
你沒說你已已經
You didn't tell me you were...
- 天啊  - 羅蘭在哪兒
- Oh, my God. - Where's Lauren?
- 她在碧芙家中  - 聽著  此事和我無關
- She's at Lisa-Beth's. - Look, this has nothing to do with me.
- 我不知道  對不起  - 對不起什麼  坐下
- I didn't know. I'm terribly sorry. - What are you sorry about? Sit down.
你不生氣嗎
Don't you even get angry?
我當然生氣
I'm angry, yeah.
我非常生氣  洛夫
I'm very angry, Ralph.
若她想要你干她  你可以干我太太
You know, you can ball my wife if she wants you to.
你可以躺在她的沙發上
You can lounge around here on her sofa.
在她前夫的
In her ex-husband's...
高科技後現代主義的荒謬家中  若你想的話
...dead-tech, post-modernistic, bullshit house, if you want to...
但你不能看我該死的電視機
...but you do not get to watch my fucking television set!
天啊
For God's sake.
把電視機放下
Put the television set down.
- 我沒對你不忠  賤貨  - 也許你應該
- I never cheated on you, bitch. - Maybe you should have.
- 我應該嗎  - 你對此也有責任
- I should have? - In a way, you're a party to this.
沒錯  我要洛夫干你  因為這使我開心
Oh, yeah. I made Ralph fuck you because it makes me feel good.
我們的處境荒謬
Our situation is absurd.
- 聽著  也許我該走了  - 住口  洛夫  坐下
- Look, maybe I should... - Shut up, Ralph. Sit down!
我為何要向你把事情解釋清楚  你又做什麼了
Why is it that I have to figure things out and explain them to you? What do you do?
- 我說話算話  亦言出必行  - 哼  多麼可敬
- I say what I mean, and I do what I say. - Mm, how admirable.
- 那當然  - 可是沒什麼是和我們有關的
- You bet. - Except none of it's about us.
是的
No.
我一定是抽大麻或服興奮劑迷糊了
I may be stoned on grass and Prozac...
但你在我們的生活中猶如死了
...but you've been walking through our life dead.
我不得不作踐自己  找洛夫來終斷我們的關係
Now I have to demean myself with Ralph just to get closure with you.
護照  旅行支票  信用卡
Passports, traveler's checks, plastic.
這飛機  在洛城機場包機站十七號機庫
The plane, charter terminal, LAX, Hangar 17.
確定密碼是一零一一山嶺
Call letters are 1011 Sierra.
飛機會降落  等你五分鐘  然後便起飛
Touches down, holds for you five minutes, then splits.
飛機會通過航空局檢查等手續
The plane will stand an FAA check. Filed a flight plan, the works.
- 基斯呢  - 他走了
- Hey, where's Chris? - He's gone.
什麼
What?
他說去找莎蓮  他走了
Said he's going on his own. Went to look for Charlene.
- 是你帶他來這兒的嗎  - 是的  我帶他來了
- Didn't you bring him here? - Yeah, I brought him here.
怎麼回事
What happened?
這是個自由國家
It's a free country, brother.
晚上九時聯絡我  確保一切妥當
Check in with me at 9. Everything's still cool.
好的
All right.
我甚至不知道自己在做什麼
I don't even know what I'm doing anymore.
我知道人生苦短
I know life is short.
能活多久是運氣
Whatever time you get is luck.
你想終斷這段關係
You wanna walk?
你現在就能離開
You walk right now.
或者你自願
Or on your own...
你自願選擇跟我一起走
On your own, you choose to come with me.
我只知道
All I know is...
我無論到任何地方去  都將失去意義
All I know is there's no point in me going anywhere anymore...
因為只有我獨自一人
...if it's gonna be alone...
沒有你陪在身邊
...without you.
伊荻
Eady.
- 喂  - 雲信  我抓了個活的
- Yeah. - Yeah, Vincent, I got a live one.
好  我等著
Okay, I'll hold.
過去  讓基斯看見你
Come on, sugar. Show yourself.
- 快去啊  - 住口
- Yeah, do it. - Shut up!
只需在窗前站一秒
Now, just one second at the window...
此事便會了結
...and it's all over.
朋友
Hey, man.
- 幹嘛  - 你知道
- Yeah? - You know any, uh...
這附近有地方要出租嗎
...place to rent around here?
知道
Yeah.
那邊牆上有告示
Alberiz's Grocer on Dell Avenue got cards on the wall.
好的  謝謝
Yeah, thanks.
不是他  不是基斯
It's not him. It's not Chris.
是指揮部
Unit 2, this is Command.
攔住他  核實他的身份
Take him at the street and check him out.
收到
10-4.
- 警官  - 說
- Sergeant? - Yeah.
他叫莊·彼得  有效的身份證
This guy's John Peterson. Valid ID.
車輛登記人是布·基贊
Car's registered to the last name Bukowski, first name Gene.
向運輸署查核過  沒有不妥
Ran it to DMV. It's clean.
- 讓他走  - 收到
- Let him go. - Roger.
非常感謝  祝你晚安
Thank you very much. Have a good evening.
不是他  雲信
It's a no-go, Vince.
我們等時你想喝咖啡嗎
Would you like a cup of coffee while we wait, Mrs. Shiherlis?
那會很不錯
Yeah, that'd be nice.
- 喂  - 你有什麼消息
- Yeah? - Yeah, what do you got?
沒事發生
Nothing's happening.
- 喂  - 我是雲信
- Yeah? - Hello, it's Vincent.
有何動靜
What do you got?
沒有  榮谷去拿冰塊了
Nothing's going on. Waingro went for ice. That's it.
你知道嗎
You know what?
尼爾跑了
Neil is gone.
走了
Bam!
- 像鳥兒般飛走  - 行了  雲信  你怎麼知道
- Flying like a bird. - Come on, Vincent, how do you know?
- 我們還有機會  也許仍有時間  - 得了  我們有什麼
- We still got bait. Maybe some time! - Got, got. What do we got?
我們有什麼
What do we got?
一路順風  混蛋
Bon voyage, motherfucker.
你很了不起
You were good.
我要回酒店去
I'm going to the hotel.
我要洗澡
I'm gonna take a shower.
好好睡覺  睡一個月
Gonna sleep for a month.
來
Over here.
醒來吧
Come on, baby.
好了
Okay, okay.
不要
Shit.
讓我綁緊胳膊
Let me tighten this.
浪費生命
What a fucking waste.
好了  來了
Okay, here.
每天都有混蛋自殺  但你不是混蛋  寶貝  你不會死的
Assholes shoot themselves all fucking day. Not you, baby. Not you.
她會在哪兒  她叫羅蘭  古·羅蘭
Where would she be? Her name is Lauren, Lauren Gustafson.
她該在這兒的
I'm supposed to be here with her. But the police...
- 我要人幫忙  - 沒事兒的
- Help me. I need somebody to help... - It's okay.
我抱著你
I got you.
我抱著你呢  寶貝
I got you, baby.
你會沒事的  你會沒事的  寶貝
It'll be all right, honey. I swear. It's okay, baby.
快找醫生來  你媽媽來了
Let's get a doctor! Let's go! A doctor here! There's your mama.
- 冷靜下來  - 你媽媽在這兒
- Let's just calm down. - Your mama's here.
- 她是吸毒了嗎  - 不是
- Is she on any drugs? - No.
找精神創傷及血管醫生來
I want you to get a trauma surgeon and a vascular surgeon.
她割斷了兩條動脈  我摸不到她的脈搏
I think she cut both arteries. Also, I could hardly feel her pulse.
她的血壓很低  呼吸也很微弱  要給她插管
Her pressure's down. So is her respiration. You have to intubate her.
準備好了
It's ready.
- 最後一次見她時是什麼時候  - 我不知道
- When's the last time anybody saw her? - I don't know.
- 你在哪兒找到她的  - 浴缸
- Where did you find her? - The bathtub.
給她注射大針管的鹽水
Call Respiratory stat. Give her large-bore normal saline. Wide open.
緊按出血的血管  先輸入兩個單位O型血
Let's keep pressure on those bleeders. I need two units, O-negative.
- 查明血型後再輸入六個單位相同的  - 看來她已經竇性心律過速
- Let's type and cross her for six. - Looks like she's in sinus tach.
呼吸專家呢  我們需要幫忙
Where is Respiratory? We need more help.
快叫呼吸科醫生過來
Can you have Respiratory come now?
準備插管後照X光
Let's have x-ray ready for post-intubation chest x-ray.
嗨  你的女兒已經做好手術  正在療養室
Hi. Your daughter's out of surgery and she's in the recovery room now, okay?
她情況穩定  醫生很快會跟你說
Her vital signs are stable. The surgeon will be out to speak to you in a few moments.
- 她沒事吧  - 她很好
- She's okay? - She's doing good.
- 她會好起來的  - 她會好起來的
- She's gonna be okay. - She's gonna be okay.
- 噢  我的寶貝  - 她會好起來的  沒事了
- Oh, my baby. - She's gonna be okay. It's all right.
- 沒事了  - 她為何這樣對待自己
- It's all right. - Why'd she do this to herself? Why?
看她把自己怎麼了
Look what she did. Look what she did to herself.
好了
There.
沒事的  不會有事的
It's all right, honey. It's gonna be all right.
我在這兒  不會到別處去
I'm here. I ain't going anywhere.
- 明白嗎  - 嗯
- You understand? - Yeah.
我不會到別處去
I ain't going anywhere.
喂
Yeah?
是我
It's me.
飛機已在半空  你得準時到達
Plane's in the air now. It'll be right on time.
可信任的司機仍找不到
On the driver's end, I still can't find nobody, so that's in the trust.
還有一事
One other thing.
你問過我  所以我得告訴你
You asked, so I gotta tell you.
你找的人在候爵酒店  化名詹美臣
The guy you wanted checked into the Marquis under "Jameson"...
我看你不想找他了吧
...if you still give a shit, which I figured you wouldn't.
- 你說得對  - 那麼  再見  兄弟
- You figured right. - So, so long, brother.
多保重
You take it easy.
你自由了
You're home free.
你也保重
Take it easy.
- 什麼事  - 沒事
- What is it? - Nothing.
自由了
Home free.
- 我得解決一些事情  - 還有時間嗎
- I gotta take care of something. - Is there time?
有的
There's time.
我很快回來  讓車子開動吧
I'll be right back. Just leave her running.
- 入住登記處  - 我是房間餐飲部
- Registration. - Yeah, this is Room Service.
詹美臣要了食物  但房號弄錯了  你能告訴我嗎
A Jameson ordered a BLT. They screwed up his room number. Could you give it to me?
- 他們經常會弄錯  - 我知道
- They're always doing that. - Yeah, I know.
- 是一七三五號房  - 謝謝
- 1735. - Thank you.
請注意
Your attention, please.
現在響起火警警報
We are currently experiencing a fire alarm.
不用惶恐  不要乘坐升降機
Please do not panic. Please do not take the elevators.
該死  榮谷沒走  我留在這兒
Shit. Waingro's not moving. I'm staying here.
我查看樓梯  若有煙  便會要你走
I'm checking the stairs. If there's smoke, I'm pulling you out.
我該通知她父親嗎
What about her dad? You want me to call him?
他在內華達山脈某處
He's somewhere in the Sierras.
她選擇了你
And she chose you.
選擇在你的房間自殺
She picked your place.
這樣做是不對的  不該發生在她身上
It's not right, what happened to her.
是的
No, it's not.
好了
Ugh, okay.
是否有方法
Is there any way...
能克服我們之間的問題
...that it could work out between us?
我希望說有
I wish I could say yes, you know.
可是  到最後
But in the end...
就像你說的
You know, it's like you said:
我沉迷於  追捕我的罪犯
All I am, is what I'm going after.
我不是你想要的人
I'm not what you want, Justine.
若你要走  便走吧
Well, go on, if you have to.
不
No.
- 我會留下  - 我沒事  我可以應付
- I'll stay. - No, I'm okay. I can... I can handle this.
你保重
Just be careful.
給我打電話  讓我知道你沒事
Call me here. Let me know you're okay.
好嗎
Okay?
走樓梯
Take the stairs.
幹嘛
Yeah?
酒店保安  三樓發生火警  各樓層的人都要疏散
Security. There's a fire on 3. We have to evacuate all the floors.
我不能離開
I can't leave here.
我們何不先談一下  兄弟
Why don't we just talk about this a bit, huh, brother?
他在十七樓
He's here on 17.
看著我  看著我
Look at me. Look at me.
看著我
Look at me.
洛城警方  別動  把手放在頭上
L.A.P.D. Don't move. Put your hands on your head, now.
將我轉到五號頻道
Switch me to TAC 5.
卡索斯  JJ
Casals? JJ?
澤加  JJ
Drucker, JJ?
我在大堂接近樓梯井
I'm at the lobby level by the stairwell.
出了什麼事
What have you got?
小組搭乘另一升降機前往十七樓
Teams are moving up the other elevators to the 17th floor elevators.
因為火警警鐘響起  升降機不能用
All out of commission because of the fire alarm.
- 這裏一團糟  人山人海  - 好的  知道了
- It's a mess. People everywhere. - Fine. 10-4.
快走  不要擋道
Let's go, get out of the way.
不要擋道
Stay out of the way.
快走  快離開
Let's go. Go that way. We gotta go, all right? Go, go.
讓我來  先生
I got it, sir.
快走
Come on, come on.
快走  先生
Come on, sir.
- 小心後面  女士們  - 我搞定了
- Watch your backs, ladies. - I got it, I got it.
繼續走  夫人
Keep moving, ma'am.
走吧
Let's go.
快點  走吧
Come on, let's go.
走這邊  夫人
This way, ma'am.
後退  後退
Get back, get back.
- 把槍給我  - 是  長官
- Let me have that shotgun. - Yes, sir.
跟你說過  我不會再回到監獄
Told you I'm never going back.
是啊
Yeah.